Contact

karina.np@icloud.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karinazamora-aprn-fnp-c-enpc-702a3570 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cardiovascular Disease Sclerotherapy Pacemakers

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

CCRN

PALS

Certified DOT Medical Examiner Advance Trauma Life Support ACLS

Karina Zamora APRN,FNP-C,ENP-C

Emergency Nurse Practitioner at Envision

Greater Houston

Summary

Experienced Nurse Practitioner with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Strong healthcare services professional with a Post Masters ED/Trauma focused in Emergency Room/Trauma Nursing from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston.

Experience

AFC Franchising, LLC
Urgent Care Nurse Practitioner
January 2017 - Present (3 years 8 months)
La Porte, Texas

EmCare

Emergency Nurse Practitioner November 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months) Pearland, Texas

Envision

Emergency Nurse Practitioner November 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months) Pearland, Texas

Orion Medical Nurse Practitioner August 2012 - November 2015 (3 years 4 months) Pasadena, TX

Cardiovascular Practice NP

Memorial Hermann Health System
Critical Care Nurse RN IV
August 2002 - August 2012 (10 years 1 month)

Houston, Texas Area

ICU charge nurse Member of Rapid response team ICU RN

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston
Post Masters ED/Trauma, Emergency Room/Trauma Nursing · (2015 - 2016)

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Master's Degree, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2010 - 2012)

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Bachelor's Degree, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2009 - 2009)

San Jacinto College

Associate's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2001 - 2004)